Button, Daniel Evan; Papers apap231
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Case Files, 1965-1971; Undated; 5; 13.6 cubic ft.
  - Ducrot, Andre Armand, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 16)
  - Dunham, David, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 17)
  - Duren, Reverand Lloyd, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 18)
  - Dwyer, James - Post Office Department, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 19)
  - Dymek, Alexander - Legislation, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 20)
  - Ehrlich, Dr. Milton - State Department, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 21)
  - Elmore, Bruce, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 22)
  - Ember, Bill - U.S. Post Office Department, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 23)
  - Embler, William J. - Post Office, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 24)
  - Erceg, James H. - Department of Defense, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 25)
  - Etkin, Jack - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 26)
  - Ettore, Mancuso - Navy, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 27)
  - Ettrich, Kurt, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 28)
  - A. Evans - Federal Water Pollution Control Administration, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 29)
  - Farmer, James, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 30)
  - Farnum, John W. - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 31)
  - Ferguson, Francis - Post Office, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 32)
  - Ferguson, Hal - HEW, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 33)
  - Fichtner, Raymond - Department of State, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 34)
  - Field, Fred G. Jr. - Post Office Department, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 35)
  - Filion, Ernest L., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 36)
  - Filutowski, Raymond - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 37)
  - Fitzgerald, John T. - Air Force, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 38)
  - Fitzpatrick, Thomas - General Services Administration, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 39)
  - Flemming, John - Navy, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 40)
  - Flood, Margaret C. - Post Office Department, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 41)
  - Foran, Mrs. John - Post Office Department, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 42)
  - Forget, Paul C. - Merchant Marines, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 43)
  - Forman, Albert W. - Federal Aviation Administration, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 44)
  - Foro, Daniel M. - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 45)
  - Forstenzer, Hyman M. - Mental Hygiene, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 46)
  - Forte, Melvin - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 47)
  - Foy, Richards S. - Federal Communications Commission, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 48)
  - Fraley, Earle, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 49)
  - Frangella, James Jr., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 50)
  - Franz, Robert - Veterans Administration, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 51)
  - Fraizer, Garry Patrick, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 52)
  - Frazierm Thomas L. - Navy, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 53)
  - Frederick, Katherine, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 54)
  - Friedman, Arnold J., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 55)
  - Freisatz, Robert - HEW, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 56)
  - Freitag, Edmund - Department of Defense, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 57)
  - Furlani, Edward, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 58)
  - Futia, Frank - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 59)
  - Gallo, Richard - Marine Corps, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 60)
  - Ganales, Daniel - Civic Education, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 61)
  - Gardner, Helen - Internal Revenue Service, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 62)
  - Garland, James - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 63)
  - Garrett, Timothy, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 64)
  - Garvey, Paul R., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 65)
  - Gaut, Millard - Department of Agriculture, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 66)
  - Gavigan, Donald H. - Army - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 67)
  - Gilbride, Charles L., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 68)
  - Gildersleeve, Laverne R. - Social Security Administration, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 69)
  - Gilmore, George E. - Air Force, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 70)
  - Gingold, Louis - 100th birthday, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 71)
  - Goble, Professor Ross L. - Mayflower Transit, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 72)
  - Gravel, Mike [Alaska Senator], 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 73)
  - Greco, Victor, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 74)
  - Green, Thomas J. - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 75)
  - Gross, Eric J. - Selective Service, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 76)
  - Grounds, Louis N. - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 77)
  - Guilderland Urban Renewal Purchase of Schenectady Army Depot, Guilderland, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 78)
  - Guinn, C.L., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 79)
  - Haas, Esta - New York State Insurance, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 80)
  - Hackert, Frank - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 81)
  - Hallenbeck, Leroy - Social Security, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 82)
  - Halloran, Daniel - Prisons, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 83)
  - Halloran, Daniel F. - State Department, Korean Relief, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 84)
  - Halse, Donald - Veterans Administration, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 85)
  - Ham, Robert C. - HR 1300, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 86)
  - Hansen, Harvey A. - Employment - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 87)
  - Hanson, Lowell D. - Social Security Administration, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 88)
  - Harris, Edward - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 89)
  - Harrison, Bill, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 90)
  - Harrison, Craig S. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 91)
  - Harrison, William - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 92)
  - Hart, David M. - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 93)
  - Hartman, Bruce, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 94)
  - Harvey, Arthur J. Esquire - State Department, House of Foreign Affairs/Internal Revenue Service Committee, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 95)
  - Hasselbach, William C. - Department of State, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 96)
  - Hastings, Donald - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 97)
  - Haque, Abulkalam W. - Immigration, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 98)
  - Hauf, John R., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 99)
  - Havern, John - Navy, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 100)
  - Haworth, J.M. - Marine Corps, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 101)
  - Hayotek, Frank U., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 102)
  - Heaney, James C. - State Department, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 103)
  - Heere, Kathleen, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 104)
  - Heidrich, Kathy J. - Federal Aviation Administration, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 105)
  - Hendler, Cliff - Post Office, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 106)
  - Hendrick, Paul - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 107)
  - Herbert, Edward L. - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 108)
  - Herbert, Howard, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 109)
  - Herman, Anthony - Veterans Administration, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 110)
  - Heron, James - OEO, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 111)
  - Herrick, Davis, Becker - Post Office Department, obscene advertisements, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 112)
  - Hess, Richard L. - Navy, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 113)
  - Hesser, Irene C. - HEW, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 114)
  - Hevenor, Earle - HEW, I.R.S., and OEO, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 115)
  - Hibbard, Elton - Federal Aviation Association, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 116)
  - Higgins - Air Force, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 117)
  - Hill, Howard G. - complaint against Schenectady History Center, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 118)
  - Hillicoss, Donald Jr., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 119)
  - Hines, Donald L., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 120)
  - Hodder, Harold W. - Veterans Administration - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 121)
  - Hoegerl, John, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 122)
  - Holton, Herbert - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 123)
  - Hornberger, David - Navy, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 124)
  - Horowitz, Harry - document request, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 125)
  - Houlihan, Daniel C. Jr. - Marines, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 126)
  - Howard, H.D. - HEW, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 127)
  - Hoy, Michael S. - Air Force, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 128)
  - Hudman, Charles, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 129)
  - Hudson River Expressway - Dan Ruge Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 130)
  - Hughes, George H. - Railroad Retirement Board, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 131)
  - Hull, Joan W. Internal Revenue Service, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 132)
  - Hull, Raymond J. Jr. - Navy, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 133)
  - Hurley, Harold H. - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 134)
  - Hutton, Francis A. - Marines, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 135)
  - ICC Albany area rate increase, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 136)
  - Inter-Faith Better Homes Development Corporation, William M. Brown, 1969; Undated (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 137)
  - Ipek, Zulfikar, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 138)
  - Isabel, Arthur - FTC and Department of Commerce, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 139)
  - Jackson, James W. - Veterans, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 140)
  - Jeffrey, Donald C. - West Point, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 141)
  - Jeram, William H. - Post Office, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 142)
  - Jerome, Jerry - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 143)
  - Jochnowitz, Rose and Waxman, Irving I., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 144)
  - Johnson, Velma - Insurance, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 145)
  - Jones, Arthur F. - A.I.D., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 146)
  - Jones, Arthur J. - Navy, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 147)
  - Jones, John B., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 148)
  - Jones, Sydney T. Jr. - Post Office, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 149)
  - Jones Noe, Dorothy - birth certificate, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 150)
  - Judge, Edward D., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 151)
  - Jupin, Alan - A.E.C., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 152)
  - Kaley, Dr. Grant S. - Post Office Department, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 153)
  - Kampf, Leonard W., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 154)
  - Kaster, Elizabeth - Civil Service, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 155)
  - Kautz, Allan A. - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 156)
  - Kawola, John - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 157)
  - Kearney, Bernard - Navy, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 158)
  - Kearney, Thomas - Army, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 159)
  - Kelleher, James C. - West Point, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 160)
  - Kellogg Foundation Harold Wiggers, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 161)
  - Kennedy, James J., 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 162)
  - Kenny, Martin and Patricia, 1969 (Box 10 (5-Case Files), Folder 163)
  - Kershner, Thomas R. - Government Printing Office, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 1)
  - Keyes, William H., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 2)
  - Kilb, Ralph W. - Social Security, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 3)
  - Kilburn, Pat E. - Army, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 4)
  - King, Evelyn, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 5)
  - Kirkham, James Robert, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 6)
  - Klinoski, Carl W., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 7)
  - Knefley, Henry R. - Post Office, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 8)
  - Koblanz, Edmund A. - Post Office Department, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 9)
  - Kolad, Jeanette - HEW, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 10)
  - Konopka, Alina - Immigration, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 11)
  - Kosich, Martin O. - Army Reserve, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 12)
  - Kostyk, Dennis - Selective Service, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 13)
  - Kottke, Raymond E. - Marines - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 14)
  - Koutsakis, John Sotiriou - Immigration [private bill], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 15)
  - Kowalczyk, Joan Ann - State Department, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 16)
  - Krahula, Charles A. - Army, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 17)
  - Kranitzky, Charles W. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 18)
  - LaFalce, John J. - Navy, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 19)
  - LaMontagne, John A. - Air Force, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 20)
  - Lance, James W. Beck - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 21)
  - Lange, Alvin E. Jr., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 22)
  - Lange, Richard Allen - Selective Service, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 23)
  - Langeley, Mortage Benefits, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 24)
  - Lansing, Jeanette, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 25)
  - Lavigne, Thomas E., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 26)
  - Lawrence, Clifton A., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 27)
  - Leackfeldt, George A. - Post Office, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 28)
  - Leah, John - Labor Department, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 29)
  - Leggiero, Stephen J. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 30)
  - Leslie, Kathryn E., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 31)
  - Letters for military service - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 32)
  - Levine, Robert M. and Muriel E., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 33)
  - Lightbody, Peggy Sue, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 34)
  - Lin, Chin Ling - Immigration, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 35)
  - Link, Peter - Labor Department, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 36)
  - Linton, Brian S., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 37)
  - Livigna, Michael P. - Treasury Department, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 38)
  - Lockhart, James, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 39)
  - Lockman, Stephen - Treasury Department, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 40)
  - Loffredo, Vincent Jr. - Airman, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 41)
  - Loiselle, Roland - Army, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 42)
  - Lombardi, Julius D. - Patent Office, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 43)
  - Long B. - Post Office, mail trucks, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 44)
  - Lucas, William E., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 45)
  - Luzados, Jose S. - Immigration, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 46)
  - Lynn, Gerald - Army, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 47)
  - MacCollam, Joel A. - Selective Service, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 48)
  - MacDougal, C.A. - Army, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 49)
  - MacGowan, Charles E. - Marine Corps, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 50)
  - MacKay, James R. - Miliary, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 51)
  - Maeder, Lloyd - Internal Revenue Service, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 52)
  - Mail handling terminal - Post Office building, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 53)
  - Male, Herbert W. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 54)
  - Maletsky, Benjamin C. - Internal Revenue Service, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 55)
  - Malik, Abdul - Immigration, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 56)
  - Malossi, Mrs. Leo - State Department, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 57)
  - Manpower Administration - William Martin, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 58)
  - Manuli, Giuseppe, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 59)
  - Marchitte, Frank J. - Air National, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 60)
  - Marciniak, Martin E. Marines - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 61)
  - Markham, Wayne Stephen - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 62)
  - Mason, William, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 63)
  - Massaro, Dr. Albert for Li Chui Being -State Department (Visa), 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 64)
  - Massaro, Joseph Jr. - Army, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 65)
  - Maylunas, John - Civil Service, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 66)
  - Mayo, Robert - Bureau of the Budget, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 67)
  - Mayville, Blanche, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 68)
  - McCarthy, Patrick - Army, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 69)
  - McCashion, John H. - Civil Service and Post Office Department, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 70)
  - McDermott, James E. - West Point, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 71)
  - McGarry, Bernard P. - Marines, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 72)
  - McGibbon, David J. - Post Office, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 73)
  - McGinnis, Frank J., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 74)
  - McDonald, Robert - HUD, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 75)
  - McDowell, Sam - Justice, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 76)
  - McGovern, Joseph T. - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 77)
  - McGuire, James - Navt, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 78)
  - MacFarlane, David - HEW, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 79)
  - McKinley, Thomas - Air Force, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 80)
  - MacMahon, Catherine - AID, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 81)
  - McNeal, Carl C. - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 82)
  - McTaggart, Dianne - Interior Department, 1969; 1970 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 83)
  - Meliti, Francis, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 84)
  - Memmerth, Kurt P., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 85)
  - Mendelsohn, Robert S., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 86)
  - Merges, Robert, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 87)
  - Merin, Arthur - Post Office delivery in 29th District, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 88)
  - Metzer, Imek, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 89)
  - Michael, Florence, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 90)
  - Michaelson, Alvin - Department of the Interior, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 91)
  - Michaelson, Stephen, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 92)
  - Miller, Russell - A& E Inc., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 93)
  - Millspough, Dennis - ICC, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 94)
  - Milne, Mark J. - Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 95)
  - Miner, Kenneth D. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 96)
  - Mitchell, David A. Esquire - State Department, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 97)
  - Mitchell, Martin Donald - Navy, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 98)
  - Mitchell, Patrick, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 99)
  - Mitchell, Robert A. - Department of Transportation - includes Troy professional assistance testimony, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 100)
  - Moakler, Martin W. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 101)
  - Moffit, Douglas - State Department (Visa) [Resticted], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 102)
  - Molinary, Luis - Navy, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 103)
  - Monarchie, Philomena, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 104)
  - Montanye, Marjorie - Schwartz, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 105)
  - Montesi, John - Selective Service, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 106)
  - Moore, Allen D. - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 107)
  - Moore, Walter D. - Internal Service Revenue, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 108)
  - Morales, Carlos A. - Immigration, 1969; Undated (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 109)
  - Moran, William J. - Marines, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 110)
  - Moravec, Charles J. (RPI) - Post Office Department, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 111)
  - Mooris, James J. - Immigration, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 112)
  - Mosca, Joseph D., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 113)
  - Motta, Josephine - Immigration - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 114)
  - Mudgett, Robert C., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 115)
  - Murnane, Peter - Coast Guard, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 116)
  - Murphy, Albert - Army, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 117)
  - Murphy, Robert J. - Post Office, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 118)
  - Myren, Richard A. Dean of School of Criminal Justice - Federal Funds, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 119)
  - Napier, William H. - Veterans Administration - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 120)
  - Neighborhood facilities - Albany, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 121)
  - Nelson, Dale A., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 122)
  - Nettleton, Mrs. George - Indian Affairs/Internal Revenue Service, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 123)
  - Newman, Doris - Naval hospital conditions, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 124)
  - Nicholas, John E., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 125)
  - Noack, William W. - Post Office, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 126)
  - Nominated, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 127)
  - Nolan, Michael E., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 128)
  - Northup, Lelia, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 129)
  - Nott Street extension, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 130)
  - Novak, Walter - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 131)
  - Noveline, Robert A. - Department of Defense, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 132)
  - O'Brien, Howard - Treasury, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 133)
  - O'Brien, John L. - State Department, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 134)
  - O'Brien, James N. - Labor, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 135)
  - O'Connell, Bruce - Selective Service, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 136)
  - O'Dell, Donald R. - Banking and Currency, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 137)
  - Offensive mail inquiry, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 138)
  - Oertel, Chris - Albany Airport, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 139)
  - Ogden, Bryan - Selective Service, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 140)
  - Olds, Benjamin H. West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 141)
  - Oliveri, Anthony J. - Marine Corps, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 142)
  - Olshysky, Agnes, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 143)
  - O'Neil, Michael T., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 144)
  - Orlando, Rita - Immigration, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 145)
  - O'Shaughnessy, Michael J. - Annapolis, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 146)
  - Ossenfort, C.J. - Post Office, 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 147)
  - Ostrander, Alva E., 1969 (Box 11 (5-Case Files), Folder 148)
  - Packard, Mrs. Frank - Commemorative Stamp, 1969 (Box 12 (5-Case Files), Folder 1)
  - Pafunda, Raymond - Post Office, 1969 (Box 12 (5-Case Files), Folder 2)
  - Paladin, Arthur - Civil Service, 1969 (Box 12 (5-Case Files), Folder 3)
  - Palm, Barbara - HEW, 1969 (Box 12 (5-Case Files), Folder 4)
  - Papa, Anthony M. - Marines - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 12 (5-Case Files), Folder 5)
  - Parker, John - Army, 1969 (Box 12 (5-Case Files), Folder 6)
  - Parker, Robert Allan - Selective Service - [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 12 (5-Case Files), Folder 7)
  - Pashley, Anna M., 1969 (Box 12 (5-Case Files), Folder 8)
  - Payst, Robert, 1969 (Box 12 (5-Case Files), Folder 9)
  - Penn Central, high speed New York to Albany, 1969 (Box 12 (5-Case Files), Folder 10)
  - Penta, Dr. Arthur Q., 1969 (Box 12 (5-Case Files), Folder 11)
  - Pentak, Joseph L. - Post Office Department, 1969 (Box 12 (5-Case Files), Folder 12)
  - Perras, Agnes, 1969 (Box 12 (5-Case Files), Folder 13)